That boy is so hot!
Is he a model?
He's got really great skin, too.
My hotness is on point again today.
I'm hot, both smart and athletic,
and both beautiful and witty.
Is there a more perfect man than me?
Of course there's not!
"Of Course, My Mom..."
Today's workout regimen consists of front
planks, plank leg raises, and push-ups.
Welcome home, Maa-kun!
Would you act your age for once, you old hag?!
Owie...
How old are you?
Would you give that up already?!
Maa-kun, you dummy! I'm in the fifth grade!
Huh? Are you still half-asleep?
Oh, dear. Maa-kun, you know better
than to be mean to little girls.
Huh?!
You don't remember her?
She's Asae-neesan's little Haruka-chan.
Aunt... Asae?
Yes. Haruka-chan is your cousin, Maa-kun.
Has it been about a year
since you last saw each other?
Uh-huh...
Haruka?
Haruka? I've heard that name before.
Oh, yeah. That was right around
the time I finally got skinny.
Thank you all for gathering here today.
Eat plenty, drink plenty,
and enjoy yourselves.
What?
Masamune-oniichan!
Oh, she's that pudgy little pudding!
Man, you sure do look a lot like the loli hag.
I mean... You sure have grown in a year! Yeah!
Onii-chan!
Why did you make Mom cry again?
Wait, no! She's not—
She's not what? You horrible son!
Oh, Masamune-kun and Chinatsu-chan.
I see you're as close as ever.
Auntie?
I wish I could've had an older
brother for Haruka, too.
You've still got time, Nee-san.
You think so?
Maybe I'll give it another try.
I'll be cheering you on.
Right, Haruka-chan?
You can do it, Mommy!
Just how are you going to do that?
Guess they really are sisters.
Seriously, though, they all
look way too much alike.
Is our hag some kind of monster?
Come over here for a sec!
What is it, Chinatsu-chan?
Here, change into these.
Nice.
Very nice.
So cute!
This is the best!
Come on, now.
I can't let this continue.
So cute!
Very nice! Why don't you
two get a little closer?
Very nice!
Wait, is she calling the cops?!
Sorry for the wait!
Auntie, wait!
Wh-Who are you?!
Oh, come on, now! It's your Auntie Asae!
You lie!
Please. I just got a little serious.
Serious? What does "serious" even mean?!
Serious about what?!
Asae-neesan, you should have
Chinatsu-chan take your picture, too.
That was exactly my intention!
Yay! We all match!
It's amazing what you can do with makeup.
Makeup? This is makeup?!
Does that mean our loli hag also
looks like that because of makeup,
and she's actually...
Women are terrifying!
I don't even want to think about that!
Onii-chan, you dummy. Mom is all natural.
Right?
Wh-What?!
That's terrifying in its own right!
So, which one is your real mom?
Is it me?
It's me, of course!
It's me, duh!
It's me!
Come on, Maa-kun!
I'm telling you, it's me!
Look at me!
Please, no!
I'm so tired.
Um... You see, Maa-kun,
I wanted to be your girlfriend,
so I tried really hard to grow bigger.
Huh?
Cousins can get married.
You've got good taste. I'll give you that.
But someone else already has my heart.
Oh...
Whoops... I was a bit too straightforward.
Well, if things don't work out,
I get to be next, okay?
Huh?
The women of the Makabe
family sure are tough.
You're the last person who should say that!
"Tsunade Island, Once More."
This feels great, doesn't it?
The scent of the salt air is so rich
that it's almost suffocating.
I didn't think I'd be able
to come back this year.
We must thank Aki-sama
for inviting us over again.
Yeah! I'm sure it'll be a lot of fun again!
We'll be there soon, so get ready.
Okay.
Welcome to Tsunade Island!
Tsunade Island
We're happy to have you again this year!
Hello, Yuisaki-san.
Oh, I see you're as cute as ever, cutie boy!
"Cutie boy"...
Welcome to Aki-sama and the rest, as well.
Hello!
I may be "the rest,"
but thank you for having us.
Oh? Where's the fucking
refreshing boy from last year?
Ah...
Oh?
Did they break up? Separate?
Bye-bye my love?
Something definitely happened!
Ahem.
Get a hold of yourself, Aki-sama.
There are plenty of good men
other than that fucking boy.
Now, hit me with any venting or anything
awful you want to say about him!
Indeed...
It really is too bad about Masamune-kun.
If only that hadn't happened...
"That"?
Was the reason infidelity? DV?
Both.
Oh, my stars! My, oh, my, oh, my!
Who did he cheat with? Who did he hit?
Himself... and himself.
Huh?
He's such an idiot.
He's the worst idiot who ever lived.
I'm on top of my game again today!
Everything about me is in perfect symmetry.
I look beautiful walking or sitting.
Not to mention my hotness
is blinding as the sun.
I am truly perfec—
What...
He was so enamored by his reflection
that he crashed into a street lamp?
He actually bled? And got a concussion?
How self-loving and narcissistic can he be?!
He is the biggest fool who's ever lived!
Ah, so that's why he
couldn't come on this trip.
Oh...
I mean... Oh, I hope he
gets back on his feet soon.
What? As if I want anything to do with him.
In that case, I'll gladly
take him off your hands.
Me, too.
Y-You two can't even tell when I'm joking?!
Oh, I thought you were quite serious.
Come on! Just try on this
bikini for a second!
No!
Makabe-kun, how could you
leave me alone like this?!
I'm so sure he'd look cute in it.
Too bad.
It's not as if I don't understand how you feel...
Yes?
Are you two ready?
Yes, anytime.
What?
Whoa, what happened?
Did you finally hit puberty?
That's right. I'm not my old self anymore.
Wow, it's such a nice day today.
T-Today is quite amusing.
Something came rolling toward me.
Y-Yoshino?
Yes, Aki-sama?
I'm hungry. Could you bring
me something to eat?
Please prepare your own meal.
Yoshino's gotten quite a bit bolder.
Yoshi—
What is it?
Never mind.
Yes?
You should start brushing from the ends.
Hi, hi!
Thank you for having us over.
What?
What do you mean, "what?"
We're having a girls' night!
Talking into the wee hours
of the morning is a must!
We came all the way to the ocean!
And it's nighttime!
That makes no sense.
This calls for sweets
and relationship stories.
Yeah! Relationship stories!
And things like what our types are...
Setting that aside...
Maybe we should talk about some troubles
we can finally bring up now.
Wh-What? I'm fine with talking about
relationship things or any advice you'd need!
Since we're all here, we should...
We should...?
Study.
Yeah...
That'd be best.
Wha—
You were actually serious?
I mean, we're third-years now.
We have to prepare for entrance exams.
Let's start with kanji drills.
Hey!
There isn't enough alcohol, damn it!
What are y'all being so buddy-buddy for?
Oh, I see.
I can't be considered a girl anymore
because I've bazongaed into my thirties?
This old hag is trying way too hard?
Asking for a ring for my birthday
present was too overbearing?
A beef bowl is more than enough?!
Help...
Shut your dumbass mouth!
Oh, I'm aware.
Love is just an illusion.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Some people just wake up from
the dream faster than others!
Hey! Aki! Sama!
You understand, don't you?
You only went out with that
hot boy because he's cute.
You wouldn't have done it if he were a fatty!
How about you? Would you date a fatty?
Er, um...
I'd have no issue as long as they were healthy.
I'd still go out with them.
You there!
You averted your eyes just now, didn't you?
You only like attractive people,
don't you?! You terrifying child!
I'd love to hear what you'd have to say.
Agreed!
You terrifying child!
Makabe-kun, save me...
Hello?
So, how are you doing?
Okay, I guess.
How are things over there?
Fine. We're having fun.
It's not as though I have to worry about
how you're holding up,
or if you'll run into another pole.
It's a very nice feeling.
So you're lonely?
Of course I'm lonely, you dummy.
"Cinderella After Twelve"
Onee-chan.
Here. Gifts from Tsunade Island.
Oh, right. Thanks. Did you have fun?
Somewhat.
I see. Don't you have the day off today?
Your trip to Tsunade Island
counted as work, didn't it?
I mean, I can understand that you feel
more comfortable wearing that outfit.
Pick whatever you like and try it on.
Huh?
This is way too mature for me.
It won't look good.
What are you talking about?
We're sisters. Of course it'll look good on you.
I don't think...
Not quite right, huh?
Hold on.
Onee-chan...
I know.
Stay perfectly still.
Otherwise, you'll see blood.
We should probably trim your bangs a bit.
Here.
There.
There we go.
Th-This is torture.
And you're all done.
You can open your eyes now.
I guess we can't do much about you
looking like an errand girl,
but today's your day off,
so go do something for yourself.
Huh?
Off you go.
Since I was always doing whatever
Aki-sama needed me to do,
I never got to carry a tiny purse like this.
I always wore flat shoes so that
I could rush to her side at any time.
I never did my nails, either.
Welcome.
It's sweet.
Is it to your liking?
I wonder why I can't find this fun.
Thank you!
That was nice.
Yeah, how fun!
Let's go over there.
Sure.
Oh, right.
Because when I finally let myself be selfish,
I still wasn't able to get
the one thing that I wanted.
Balloons!
I'll go get you one!
I-I'm sorry!
You can have it.
Thank you!
Oh, sorry.
Did you see her? She was super cute!
Huh? Where?
I don't think I saw her.
Sorry, Onee-chan.
It's fine, but are you sure you
want to come back already?
Yeah.
Honestly, what am I going to do with you?
But it was a little bit fun.
I had been wanting to be
prettier... on my own.
Really?
Yeah.
So you're finally getting serious?
I'll become prettier, be a better woman...
Yup, yup...
...make them fall for me, and then dump them.
What?
Just kidding.
It's Aki-sama.
Who knew she had that side to her?